{
    "id": "127043c27e2b461dbd2e930d2a7784c0",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is time you ………………………… that mole checked.",
            "description": "A simple past is used after it is time to refer to the present or future. ",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "got",
                "should get"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There …………………………… be a tea stall in that corner.",
            "description": "Used to can be used to talk about past states. Would cannot be used with this meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "used to",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………… to be a singer.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about needs, wants, desires, aspirations etc.",
            "answers": [
                "aspires",
                "is aspiring",
                "aspire"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. never violate the rules.",
            "description": "Must shows strong obligation.",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If she left home at six, she ……………………………… be here soon.",
            "description": "Should shows logical possibility. ",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "need",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There are no secrets between you and …………………………….",
            "description": "Between is a preposition. A pronoun used after the preposition should be in its object form.",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She patted ………………………… on the back for completing the project on time.",
            "description": "When the subject and object refer to the same person, the reflexive pronoun (herself, yourself etc.) is used instead of the object pronoun. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "herself",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited ………………………… hours and then I went home.",
            "description": "For is used with duration.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………. playing to the best of our ability, we could not win the match.",
            "description": "Either despite or in spite of can be used here.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Despite of",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They congratulated her …………………………………. her success.",
            "description": "Either for or on is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you always shouting ………………………….. me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. of them was there.",
            "description": "All and some should be followed by a plural verb.",
            "answers": [
                "None",
                "All",
                "Some"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}